Cesar Siguencia

cd.siguencia@gmail.com ■ (646) 457-7006 ■ New York, NY 10031

Portfolio: cesarsiguencia.github.io/my-react-portfolio Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/cesar-siguencia GitHub: github.com/cesarsiguencia

Full stack web developer with a strong background in education and passionate about developing productivity and social media apps. Outspoken team player with extensive experience in customer service and data management. Strengths include creativity, availability to others, leadership, ability to learn quickly, and having a "whatever it takes" attitude.

SKILLS & LANGUAGES

Front-End	Databases	General
HTML5 CSS3 JavaScript React	SQL MySQL PostgreSQL	Audio/video production IT Microsoft
Handlebars JQuery Bootstrap	MongoDB	Office Google Drive TDD OOP
Back-End	Developer Tools	Languages
Back-End Node Express Python Sequelize	Developer Tools Git GitHub CLI VS Code	Languages Spanish (Fluent) Chinese

FULL STACK PROJECTS

iCanFixIt ■ <u>icanfixit-by-cs-a17c7a1ff29b.herokuapp.com</u> ■ <u>Source Code</u>

React, MongoDB, Express, Node, Mongoose, Bootstrap, Cloudinary API, JavaScript

A MERN app for my side business repairing broken Apple devices, including screen and battery services on iPhones

10000 Days ■ cs-10000-days-33ee2045b3a6.herokuapp.com ■ Source Code

Handlebars, Sequelize, PostgreSQL, Node, Express, JavaScript

An MVC app for invited guests to RSVP and interact with each other for a one of a kind upcoming social gathering

Technify In Python ■ <u>technify-by-cs.up.railway.app</u> ■ <u>Source Code</u>

Python, Flask, PyMySQL, SQLAlchemy, Bcrypt, JavaScript

An easy to use social media app for developers to communicate and share worthy tech related links

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Certificate: Full Stack Web Development / 24 weeks ■ Columbia University, New York, NY	2021 - 2022
Bachelor of Arts: Sociology Music Chinese ■ Bowdoin College, Brunswick, ME	2014 - 2018

WORK EXPERIENCE

Operations Coordinator Mount Carmel Holy Rosary School, New York, NY

October 2021 - July 2023

Promoted to this position by school principal in the 21-22 academic year. Continued to fulfill all tasks from previously held Operations Associate role

- Managed tuition collection systems, financial aid, school metrics, deposits reconciliation, newsletters, and IT support
- Managed small office team and ensured impeccable customer service was provided to all visitors and parents
- Led and prepared various student recruitment events, showcases, and faculty events
- Key planner of school operation logistics, protocols, schedules, field trips, sanitation and sustainability maintenance

Operations Associate Mount Carmel Holy Rosary School, New York, NY

November 2018 - October 2021

Promoted to serve as the school's video producer and author of the school's weekly newsletter

- Aided the Director of Operations with finances management, inventory, human resources, and front office service
- Analyzed and collected general student data, school metrics, employee payroll, and customer payments daily
- Supported admissions by collecting inquiries, applications, student registrations, and led building tours for visitors